Gozar/Gorz is a controlled local-first prototype release candidate for Android UX, local profile lifecycle, platform automation, evidence, and review.
The safety boundary is explicit: this is not a production VPN, not a public routing product, and not suitable for sensitive communication.
The four-phase roadmap closes with Phase 4: controlled release readiness across Android, platform assets, detection, reporting, and reviewer evidence.
The Android Home screen introduces the controlled demo state, offline mode, route safety, evidence, diagnostics, and safety pause.
The offline connect flow demonstrates local session lifecycle behavior without relying on public infrastructure.
The confidence screen shows deterministic scoring and explainable local signals.
The route policy screen shows the applied local route, 10.77.0.0/24, and blocked unsafe routes.
Evidence Package V2 includes redaction summary, checksum, diagnostics, route policy, and safety status.
Safety Pause blocks new sessions, records audit events, and appears in diagnostics and evidence.
Terraform and Kubernetes assets describe local lab infrastructure, ClusterIP services, overlays, and NetworkPolicy.
Prometheus and Grafana assets provide controlled release observability views and alerts.
SIEM-style detection rules evaluate redacted sample events and generate a local detection report.
The incident summary uses deterministic offline logic and does not call an external model by default.
GitHub Actions document CI, Android, emulator smoke, readiness, Terraform, Kubernetes, detection, and release candidate workflows.
The production readiness report marks the review package ready while production-ready for real use remains NO.
The final position is a controlled prototype release candidate for demo, portfolio, research, and platform-security review.